大才女驾到
Here she is!
感谢你们出席我的毕业礼
Thanks for being there, you guys.
我们怎么会错过呢 亲爱的
We wouldn't have missed it, sweetie.
你的演讲真精彩
Your speech was fantastic.
你的声音出了什么问题
What's wrong with your speech?
有那么明显吗 我...
Oh, is it that obvious? I...
我戴了成人牙套
I got adult braces!
你确定吗
Are you sure?
看起来好像不合你的尺寸
'cause they don't seem like they fit right.
我觉得你这么做很勇敢
I think it's a bold step,
我支持你为自我提升而做出的努力
And I support you in your journey of self-improvement.
不行 你不能把头发拉直
No, you're not getting your hair straightened.
你爸爸真的很希望他能到场
You know your dad wishes he could be here.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我就在这呢
I'm right here!
我让安迪帮我连上线了
I had Andy set me up
这样我就能和你们一同庆祝
so I could be here with you all.
我只是负责把电源接上
I just had to plug him in.
当年我在医院不得不拔了我父亲的呼吸机
It was a nice reversal from when I had to pull the plug
现在能做相反的事感觉挺好
on my dad in the hospital.
菲尔出差时
While he was away on a business trip,
患了严重的耳部感染
Phil got a terrible ear infection,
医生说如果他坐飞机
and the doctors said he
可能会造成耳膜破裂
could burst an eardrum if he flew.
错过艾丽克斯的毕业典礼让我好难受
I was devastated to miss Alex's graduation,
但后来我意识到我不需要错过
until I realized I didn't have to.
我把手机举了两个小时
I got to hold up my phone for two hours
就为了给菲尔直播毕业礼
so Phil could see the graduation live.
我敢说我是那里唯一一个没穿裤子的父亲
Bet I was the only dad there not wearing pants.
这玩意儿太棒了有没有
How great is this thing, huh?
非常方便
It's so convenient.
感觉如同我就在现场陪你们呢
It's like I'm right there in the room...with you guys.
有人吗
Hello?
人呢
歌洛莉亚 你可以告诉你的表亲
Gloria, would you tell your cousin
不要再到处乱扔垃圾了吗
to stop leaving his trash everywhere?
他这么胡闹有五天了
It's been five days of this nonsense.
到我家来 吃光我的食物
He comes in here, eats all my food,
喝光我的酒
drinks all my booze,
连个碗都不知道洗
and never so much as does a dish.
是的 和那边
Oh, yes, so different
那些白人在做的事完全不同呢
from what all those white people over there are doing.
你对你家这些好吃懒做的蠢货
You got a blind spot for the deadbeat
容忍度还真高
yahoos in your family.
他才不是蠢货 不要当着他的面这么说
He's not a yahoo, and don't say that in front of him!
他不会说英语
He doesn't speak english!
他能听懂
He understands it.
真的吗
Oh, really?
着火了 快跑 着火了
Fire! Run! Fire!
你瞎说什么呢 贝丝 别走
You're being ridiculous, Beth. Don't go.
你真贴心 但我不想打扰你们
Oh, you're so sweet, but I don't want to intrude,
所以我们晚点再见吧
so I'll just see you guys later.
歌洛莉亚 告诉她她可以留下
Oh, Gloria, tell her she can stay.
你当然可以留下了
Of course you can stay.
我们喜欢你来做客 尤其是乔
We love having you here, especially Joe.
你是他的新宠
You're his new favorite.
我曾经是他的最爱
I used to be his favorite
后来我告诉了他 我陪他玩是拿了钱的
until I told him I get paid to hang with him.
我只是觉得他有知情权
I just felt like he had a right to know.
说实话 我之前以为自己喜欢上安迪了
If I'm being honest, I thought I was into Andy.
后来他的女友贝丝过来看他
Then his girlfriend, Beth, came into town,
她人很好 他们在一起很幸福
and she's really sweet and they're great together.
所以本着毕业季的精神
So, in the spirit of graduation,
我要正式放下他走向未来了
I'm officially moving on.
而且和我自己的毕业季不同
And, unlike my actually graduation,
这次没有怀孕惊吓
there's no pregnancy scare.
好的
All right.
穿好了
Good.
你确定要给他穿这件吗
Uh, are you sure about that outfit?
怎么总是发生这种事
Why does this keep happening?
反正不是因为乔穿得像个成年人
Well, it's not because Joe dresses like an adult.
我穿得很像成年人
I dress like an adult.
电台司令演唱会那次你穿着闪光运动鞋
You wore light-up sneakers to a Radiohead concert.
是的 而我们有没有走散呢
Yes. And did we ever get separated?
我不是没有尝试过甩掉你
Not for lack of trying.
天哪
Oh, my God.
海莉 你不知道我扔那双鞋扔了多少次
Haley, the number of times I've thrown those shoes away.
它们在垃圾堆里太容易被找到了
They're just too easy to spot in the trash.
是的 继续笑吧
Oh, yes. Yuk it up.
我去给他找件新上衣
I'm gonna go get him a new shirt.
《金发姑娘》
"Goldilocks".
这故事我妈妈给我读过无数次
My mom read this to me a thousand times.
我一直不理解
I just never understood
那个小姑娘是怎么幸免于难的
how that little girl got away with it.
什么意思
What do you mean?
如果我是故事里的那只熊
Well, if I were a bear
有人闯进我家
and somebody broke into my house,
睡了我的床 吃了我的食物
laid in my bed, and ate my food,
我会把她的小细胳膊扯下来的
I'd rip her skinny little arms off.
只是麦片粥而已 对吧
Well, it's just porridge, right?
是我的麦片粥
It's my porridge.
回来啦
There he is.
真是怪了 我有一件一模一样的T恤
This is crazy, but I have this same shirt.
你真可爱
You're so adorable.
他是不是很可爱
Isn't he adorable?
是吧
Y-yeah.
我应该更经常离开房间的
I should leave the room more often.
不要
No!
奶酪可以搅拌吗
Can you blend cheese?
我想不行 我也不想尝试
I don't think so, and I don't want to try it.
我就是想喝杯奶昔或什么的
I just want a smoothie or something.
你们好
Hey, guys!
-天哪 -老天
- Oh, my gosh. - Oh, god.
猜怎么着 他们接受了你们的出价
Guess what. They accepted your offer.
天哪 太棒了
Oh, my gosh! That's fantastic!
出什么价
What offer?
我们要买下我们楼上那间公寓
We're buying the apartment upstairs from us.
我们要扩充空间
We're gonna expand,
给家里弄个像样的客房
put in a proper guest room,
-还有办公室 -没错
- a home office. - Yeah.
-很多空间 -是的
- So much space. - Yeah.
恭喜了
Congrats!
我要趁你再往屏幕上喷口水之前滚开了
I'm gonna roll away before you spit on my screen again.
太棒了是不是
Isn't that great?
是啊 很棒 很棒
Yeah. Oh, so great, so great.
我以为米奇尔因为买下楼上的公寓这事
I thought Mitchell would be more excited
应该会更激动些的
about the unit upstairs.
他有什么心事
Something is going on with him.
最近他对我有些冷漠
He's been more distant lately.
过去两周里
For the last two weeks,
他对下面的公寓也不大感兴趣
he hasn't been that interested in the unit downstairs, either.
那是什么
What's that?
菲尔 没什么
Phil, nothing.
只是我要送给艾丽克斯的礼物
It's just a little gift I got Alex.
但我们已经送过礼物了啊
But we already gave her our present.
16件套拉杆箱超赞的
That 16-piece luggage set was a real winner.
这是母亲送给女儿的礼物
This is more of a mother-daughter thing.
是个钥匙扣 上面有一张我和艾丽克斯
It's just a key chain with a picture of me and Alex
在她第一天上学时的合照
on her first day of school.
我想要她拥有一件
I wanted her to have something
能提醒她我有多爱她的东西
that reminded her of how much I love her.
何不直接唱我给她写的那首歌啊
Why don't we just sing that song I wrote her?
因为我不想唱那首无聊的歌
Because I don't want to sing that lame song.
无聊 好吧
Lame. Okay.
菲尔 没搞错吧 拜托
Phil, really? Come on.
只有你才能伤到机器人
Only you could hurt a robot!
你需要帮助吗
You, uh -- you need some help?
好啊
Sure.
我在想...
So, um, I was wondering --
贝丝跟你说了我的什么事吗
Um, has Beth said anything to you about me, about...
不喜欢我什么的
not liking me?
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
贝丝非常喜欢你
Beth's obsessed with you.
她总是说
She's always like,
"海莉好可爱 我真想咬她的脸"
"Haley's so cute. I just want to bite her face."
天啊
Oh, my God.
她问我你在哪里工作
She asked me where you work,
晚上去哪里 是不是一个人远足
where you go at night, whether you hike alone.
实际上她很关心你
She's actually very concerned about you.
有没有可能...
Or is it possible --
你们聊些什么呢
What are you guys talking about?
我只喜欢韩国男人
How I'm only into Korean dudes.
好啊 亲爱的
Oh, hey, honey.
好啊 菲尔
Hey, Phil.
别转过来 装淡定
Hey, don't turn. Be cool, be cool.
我需要你取消公寓这单生意
I need you to make this apartment thing go away.
-什么 -我说了 装淡定
- What? - I said, "be cool."
你为什么想取消啊
Why do you want it to go away?
办公室裁减了预算
We had some budget cuts at the office,
有几个人被辞退了
and a bunch of us got laid off.
我没有告诉小卡 因为
Now -- now, I didn't tell Cam because...
我觉得很丢脸 但也因为我知道
I was embarrassed, but also because I knew --
我知道我分分钟就能找到新工作
I knew I would get another job like that.
已经过去一个月了 现在好尴尬
It's been a month, and -- and now it's just weird
我一开始没告诉他这事
that I didn't tell him in the first place,
所以每天早上我假装去上班
So every morning, I leave for work.
嗨哟嗨哟 我去上班啦
Well, heigh-ho, heigh-ho. It's off to work I go.
我每天先是发简历
I send out my resume.
像大部分对配偶隐瞒事实的
And then, like most unemployed people
失业人员一样
hiding the truth from their spouses,
我会去公园
I go to the park.
有一天 我遇见了斯宾塞
And then, one day, I met Spencer.
你好
Hello.
现在我每天都和斯宾塞下棋
And now I play checkers with spencer.
不
No!
还有他最好的朋友 乔治
And his best friend, George,
它帮我克服了一直以来对鸟的恐惧
who helped me get over my lifelong fear of birds.
痒痒 别闹了
That tickles. Stop it! Stop it!
米奇尔 你可以告诉我
Mitchell, you can talk to me.
我是房地产经纪人
I'm a realtor.
我需要你取消交易 好吗
I need you to kill the deal, okay?
别告诉小卡
Don't tell Cam.
米奇
Mitch...
那是怎么回事 米奇尔说了什么
What was that about? What did Mitchell say?
我是闻到了杰的拿手排骨吗
Do I smell Jay's famous ribs?
菲尔 菲尔
Phil. Phil.
冷静 歌洛莉亚需要餐巾环
Calm down. Gloria needs napkin rings.
我要举起你 你看看高层架子
I'm gonna hold you up. You can check the high shelves.
使劲举 我中午吃了很多
Lift with your legs. I had a big lunch.
我没看见有餐巾环
I don't see any napkin rings.
只看到一个写着西班牙语的盒子
I just see a box with some Spanish written on it.
可能就是了
Oh, that's probably it.
克罗基特和塔布斯 那可是海洛因
Crockett and Tubbs! That's heroin!
什么
What?!
你懂的 白粉 白面 四号仔
You know, horse, smack, hell dust.
我知道外号 我看过《侦探科杰克》
I know the nicknames. I've watched "Kojak".
我敢肯定是歌洛莉亚的那个人渣表亲
I guarantee that low-life cousin of Gloria's
藏在这里的
stashed this up there.
杰 餐巾环呢
Jay, where are the napkin rings?
我给你们一点隐私吧
I'll give you guys some privacy.
瞧瞧你表亲在这里藏了什么
Look what your cousin's hiding in here.
这是我的马[白粉]
That's my horse.
这是你的
That's yours?
是啊 我从哥伦比亚带来的
Yes, I brought it back from Colombia.
天啊 我娶了个贩毒集团的人吗
My god. I married into a drug cartel?
这是我死去的马儿加乌乔的骨灰
These are the ashes of my dead horse, Gaucho.
我小时候养的他
I had him when I was a little girl.
你觉得这是毒品
You thought that these were drugs
而且是我表亲的吗
and that they belong to my cousin?
不然我该怎么想啊
Well, what was I supposed to think?
我受够了 杰
I am sick of this, Jay.
你把我的家人当做罪犯
You treat my family like they're criminals.
好像他会带价值十五万美金的海洛因
Like he would bring $150,000 worth of
来这里一样
heroin into this house!
你怎么知道这值多少钱
How do you know how much --
怎么 我就不能知道街头黑市价吗
What?! I can't know street value?!
艾丽克斯 亲爱的 能耽误你一会儿吗
Alex, honey, could I borrow you for a minute?
稍等
One sec.
米奇舅舅 这太棒了
Uncle Mitch, this is amazing.
你居然留着这些东西
I can't believe you kept all of this.
没什么特别的啦
Oh, it's nothing special.
里面是你给我写的每一张便条和画的每一幅画
of every note and drawing you ever made me.
你在开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
你好
Oh, oh. Hola.
这很不错
This is good.
这是你四岁时
This is a report card
给我做的明信片
that you made for me when you were 4,
你给我这个舅舅打了B-的分数
And you gave me a b-minus as an uncle.
我很生气 因为你投了拉尔夫·纳德的票
I was mad because you wasted your vote on Ralph Nader.
而今天你拿到了A+
But today, you get an A-plus,
因为这是有史以来最有心思的礼物
because this is the most thoughtful gift ever.
米奇尔 你怎么会有时间做这个的
Oh, Mitchell, where do you even find the time for this?
所以这个是放这里还是这里呢
So, this one -- here or here?
我不确定
I don't know.
放这里如何
What about here?
斯宾塞
Spencer!
各位 我随口问一句
Hey, guys, so, a random question,
你们中有谁
but, um, do any of you
觉得贝丝怪怪的吗
get kind of a weird vibe from Beth?
就是有点不正常那种
You know, like maybe something's a little off?
贝丝 怎么会 她超棒的
Beth? No. She's an angel.
对啊 她人可好了
Yeah, she seems super-sweet.
你还真是不怕用带S的词
You're really not shying away from those "S" words, are you?
所以没人觉得
S-so, no one thinks
贝丝有点诡异吗
that Beth has maybe, like, a slightly psychotic side?
我知道是怎么回事了
I see what's going on here.
有人嫉妒了
Somebody's jealous
因为她不再是这里
'cause she's not the only pretty girl
唯一的小美女了 对吧
around here anymore, hmm?
我可谢谢你了 老妈
Thanks, mom.
贝丝超性感
Beth's super-hot.
要是海岸巡逻队员都长那样
If everyone in the coast guard looks like that,
我也去报名
sign me up.
只在周末工作对吧
It's just on the weekends, right?
算了 你们都真没用
Forget it. You're all useless.
-是谁啊 -工作上的事
- Who was that? - Oh, it's just work.
我有一条绝对的底线
There is a line that I will not cross.
只要碰了他的手机 就是怀疑他的忠贞
As soon as I touch that phone, I'm a suspicious spouse,
我不是那种人
and that is not me.
所以我跟服务员说
So, I say to the waitress...
我看到你倒的是普通咖啡
"I saw you pour from the regular pot."
然后她说 不是
And, um, she's like, "Nope.
我倒的是低咖啡因的
I, uh, poured from the decaf pot".
天哪
You know? Oh, my gosh.
我来捡
Let me get that.
快点说 别吊我胃口
Come on. Don't leave me hanging.
你是不是整晚都没睡着
Were you up all night?
"跟你玩得很开心 斯宾塞"
"Had fun with you. Spencer.
"周一见 斯宾塞"
See you ,Monday. Spencer.
"笑脸 斯宾塞"
Smiley face. Spencer".
斯宾塞是谁
Who is Spencer?!
邓先生
Hey, Mr. D.
我们能聊一下吗
Can we talk?
当然 想喝点儿什么
Sure thing. What'll you have?
怎么了
What's up?
我接到了
So, I've been...
贝丝的暗示
getting some signals from Beth
她想让我求婚
that she wants me to propose.
真是激动人心
That's exciting.
对啊 我连戒指都准备好了
Yeah. I even have ring.
那你还犹豫什么呢
So, what's the hold-up?
其实 还有另外一个女孩
Well... there's this other girl,
我感觉自己被她深深地吸引
and I feel like I have a serious connection with her,
可我不知道她是怎么想的
but... I just don't know how she feels.
安迪 我当年跟克莱尔约会时
Andy, back when I was dating Claire,
我想过假如哪天在自助洗衣店里
I used to think, "What if I'm in the laundromat one day,
罗宾·吉文斯[泰森前妻]走进来
and Robin Givens walks in?"
她问我要一个25美分硬币
She asks me for a quarter.
我拿给她
I hand her one.
我们手指相触
Our fingers linger.
她会想在拳王泰森之后
She wonders if maybe after "Iron Mike",
她最渴望的其实是
what she's really yearning for
一位温柔绅士的触碰
is the touch of a gentler man.
我没听明白
I'm not following.
人天性就喜欢幻想不同的人生
It's natural to wonder about a different path,
可如果你真的爱贝丝 那就应该求婚
but if you truly love Beth, you should propose.
你说的没错 我会的
You're right. I'll do it.
海边有个她很喜欢的地方
There's this place she loves by the ocean.
我要带她去那里 在夕阳中求婚
I'll take her there and propose at sunset.
真棒
Great!
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
来抱一个
Bring it in.
拜托 去开房吧
Oh, come on. Get a roomba.
亲爱的 钥匙链不够好
Honey, the key chain was a bust.
我需要别的东西 快点 想一个
I need something else. Quick. Come on.
明白 你想唱那首歌
Got it. You want to sing the song.
幸好我旅行中带着尤克里里
Good thing I brought my ukulele on the trip.
旅行
Trip!
艾丽克斯小的时候 我曾带她去
When Alex was little, I took her for brunch
北边的那个荷兰小镇吃早午餐
at that cute little Dutch town up north.
我可以再带她去一趟
I-I could take her there again.
只属于我们母女的旅程 太棒了
A trip for just the two of us. It's perfect.
*当你没有...*
*When you don't --*
克莱尔
Claire?
艾丽克斯 宝贝 你还记得
Alex, honey, do you remember --
天哪 妈妈
Oh, my God, Mom!
外公送我欧洲之旅庆祝毕业
Grandpa got me a trip to Europe for my graduation!
我想让她知道她对我有多重要
I just wanted her to know how much she meant to me.
我讨厌这一家子
I hate this family.
菲尔 我需要跟你进行男人之间的谈话
Phil, I need to talk to you, man-to-man.
我觉得米奇尔出轨了
I think Mitchell's having an affair.
什么
What?
我翻他钱包的时候
I was going through his wallet
找到了笑袅酒店的收据
and I found a receipt to the Avian Hotel.
有可能是他跟情人
It's probably some fancy French place
周末偷偷约会的
where he's meeting his lover
某个高级法式酒店
for their secret weekly rendezvous.
他跟你聊过关于楼上那套房的事吗
Has he said anything to you about the unit upstairs?
你倒吸气了
You gasped.
因为你先倒吸气了啊
Only because you did.
菲尔 告诉我你知道什么
Phil, tell me what you know right now.
我什么都不知道 放我下来
I don't know anything. Put me down.
跟你老公谈谈
Talk to your husband.
这是我的钱包 你没见过我
This is my wallet. You never saw me.
斯黛拉 不要 坏孩子
Stella, no. Bad girl.
坏孩子 斯黛拉 不要
Bad girl. Stella, no.
斯黛拉 不要
Stella, no.
莉莉在台子上撒了些果汁
Lily spilled some juice on the counter.
我该搜搜看她身上有没有枪吗
Should I frisk her for guns?
老天
Oh, geez.
打扰了
Oh, sorry.
杰 不要
Jay, no!
海莉
Haley!
快过来看
Come check it out.
我在教卢克和曼尼一些
I was just showing Luke and Manny
我在海岸警卫队训练学到的技能
some things that I learned in coast guard training.
你好美
You look so pretty.
好了 曼尼 把这支笔从我手上拿走
All right, Manny, take this pen from me.
你是要我就这么拿吗
So, you just want me to grab it?
看见了吧
See?
如果有人
That's what you do
要抢走属于你的东西 你就用这招
when someone tries to take something that's yours.
帅爆了
Awesome.
到我了
My turn.
怎么回事 我拿到笔了吗
What happened? Did I get the pen?
你的头发烧着了
Hey, your hair's burning!
什么
What?!
我的天
Oh my God!
你的头发
Ay! Your hair!
我来搞定
I got it!
灭了 灭了
It's out! It's out!
怎么回事
What happened?
一定是被那根蜡烛烧着了
It must have been that candle.
你为什么坐得离它那么近
Why'd you sit so close to it?
她让我坐这儿的
She told me to!
贝丝 多亏有你在这里
Ay, Beth, thank God that you were here.
很高兴我能帮上忙
I'm just glad I could help.
这里发生的事情太疯狂了
It's getting crazy in here.
你想不想去泳池里冷静一下
You want to cool things off in the pool?
杰
Jay!
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
原来你在这儿
There you are.
我跟你说 你肯定不
Okay, you are -- you're never...
你肯定不会相信我爸做了什么
You're never gonna believe what my dad did.
-把你锁在厕所里吗 -不是
- Lock you in the bathroom? - No.
他送艾丽克斯欧洲行作为毕业礼物
He gave Alex a trip to Europe for her graduation present.
这么一来我周末带她去
There's no way I can now give her
吃荷兰煎饼球的计划就太逊色了
a weekend of Dutch pancake balls after that.
你能把门打开吗 我有点透不过气的感觉
Can you open the door? I'm feeling claustrophobic.
菲尔 你现在在西雅图的酒店房间里
Phil, you're in a hotel room in Seattle.
我真的绝望了 快点教我唱那首歌
I'm desperate. Just teach me the song.
哎哟喂 看看这是谁在巴结我啊
Well, well, well. Look who came crawling back.
赶紧教我唱
Just teach it to me.
好哒
Okay.
这首歌叫做《有事就找艾丽克斯》
It's called "Go Ask Alex".
*如果你有单词不知道意思*
*When you don't know what a word means*
*就找艾丽克斯*
*Go ask Alex*
*如果你有牛仔裤需要缝边*
*If you need someone to hem your jeans*
*就找艾丽克斯*
*Go ask Alex*
不敢相信我居然要说这话
I can't believe I'm even saying this,
但把"有牛仔裤需要卷边"换成
but instead of "Hem your jeans",
"有绿叶菜需要蒸好"岂不是更好
could it be "Steam your greens"?
不能改
No, it can't.
唱到第四分钟牛仔裤这段要重复
The jeans come back at the 4-minute mark.
海莉
Haley.
你怎么样了
How you feeling?
我听说你的头发烧着了 好可怕
Heard about the hair fire. Sounds scary.
可怜的娃
Poor thing.
我准备了个小礼物 放在你车上了
I left you a gift on your car to help you feel better.
是红色的那辆 对吧
It's the red one, right?
你能帮我启动一下我的车子吗
Hey, can you do me a favor and go start my car?
好吧
Uh, I guess.
谢谢
Thanks.
他没死 没事没事
He's alive. It's fine.
好啦 大家都过来一下
Okay, everybody gather 'round.
菲尔和我给我们聪明的毕业生艾丽克斯
Phil and I have prepared something very special
准备了一个特别的贺礼
for our brilliant graduate, Alex.
你准备好了吗
Okay, you ready?
*当你...*
*When you...*
怎么搞的 怎么没声音
Why is that not -- okay, there's no sound.
菲尔 亲爱的 你那边没声音
Phil, honey? There's no sound.
趁着克莱尔修理机器人菲尔这会儿
Okay, so, while Claire fixes robot Phil,
我来致个辞
I make toast.
我刚刚来到这个家时
When I first came into this family,
我以为我永远不会被你们接纳
I didn't think I was ever going to be accepted.
直到有一天
Then, one day,
艾丽克斯要写关于某个家庭成员的报告
Alex needed to write a report about a family member,
她选了我
and she picked me.
那是我第一次觉得自己真的是家中一员
That was the first time I really felt part of the family.
艾丽克斯 你是第一个向我示好的人
Ay, Alex, you were the first one to reach out to me,
我永远不会忘记的
and I will never forget that.
他们都说你是最聪明的
They all call you the smart one,
但是对我来说 你是最善良的
but to me, you're the kind one.
生命中有你 我真的太幸运了 宝贝
I'm so lucky to have you in my life, baby.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
说得太好了
Hear, hear.
终于听到了
Oh, there you are.
*当你有单词不知...*
*When you don't know what a word -- *
别唱了 别唱了 我们现在不唱了
No, not doing it, not doing it. We're not -- not doing it.
等我一下
One second.
歌洛莉亚 听你致辞
Gloria, watching you give that toast,
我意识到你把我的家人视为你的亲人
I see you treat my family like your own.
你说的很对
And you're right.
我也要对你表亲好一点
I need to treat your cousin nicer.
谢谢你 杰
Thank you, Jay.
告诉阿尔曼多我很抱歉没有好好招待他
Tell Armando I'm sorry I haven't been more welcoming to him.
告诉他他是个好人
Tell him he's a great guy.
他想在这待多久就待多久
And he can stay as long as he wants.
我们原谅你了
We forgive you.
真的吗 要不我给他个拥抱什么的
You sure? Maybe I can give him a little hug or something.
不 太过头了
No, it's too much.
走好
Bye-bye.
我受够了 我必须要搞清楚
Okay, I've had enough. I need to know.
这个金贵的斯宾塞是谁
Who is this precious Spencer?
天呐 你怎么知道斯宾塞的
Oh, God. How do you know about Spencer?
也就是说你承认了
So you admit it.
你有外遇了
You are having an affair.
-什么 -是因为我的牙套对不对
- What? - It's the braces, isn't it?
我把你吓走了 我实在太丑了
I've driven you to stray. I'm hideous.
小卡 你这简直是疯了
Cam, you're acting crazy.
是吗 米奇尔
Am I? Mitchell...
我发现了笑袅酒店的收据
I found the receipt to the Avian Hotel.
正确的读音是"小鸟"
That's pronounced "Ay-vee-ann."
反正听上去很寒酸
Well, it sounds seedy.
没错 那是个鸟类收容所
It is. It's a kennel for birds.
我得去那里接乔治
It's where I picked up George.
竟然还有个乔治
There's a George, too?
淡定 我指的是一只白鹦鹉[一两根鸡鸡]
Calm down. I'm talking about a cockatoo.
一两根啊 仅此而已吗 真无趣啊
One or two. Is that all? How blasé?
小卡 乔治是一只鸟
Cam, George is a bird,
斯宾塞是最近在公园里跟我一起玩的老人
and Spencer is an old man I've been hanging out with at the park,
因为我...
because I...
我被裁员了
I got laid off.
你失业了吗
You lost your job?
对不起 我...
I'm sorry. I just --
我没脸告诉你我又失业了
I couldn't tell you that I was out of work again.
我感觉自己好失败
I...I feel like such a loser.
不 别这么说 天啊
No, please. My gosh.
只要你没背着我找小三就行了
As long as you're not cheating on me,
那才是真正重要的
that's all that matters.
肯定会有其他机会的 你是个出色的律师
Something will come up. You're a great lawyer.
谢谢 我只是...
Oh, thank you. I just --
我觉得我们现在没办法买下那间公寓了
I don't think that we can get that apartment right now.
当然可以买了
Of course we can.
我们已经有首付款了
We already have the down payment.
再说我们还可以租出去呢
And you know what? We could get renters.
我们可以把它变成家庭旅馆
We could it into an Airbnb.
不是吧 每周都来不同的住客吗
Really? Different people every week?
很新鲜刺激啊 就跟电视剧《爱之船》一样
How exciting and new. It'd be like "The Love Boat".
妈 你有空吗[要第二杯吗]
Hey, Mom, have a second?
已经在喝了
Already am.
我想送你一份礼物
I wanted to give you a present.
我吗 不是吧
Me? No.
亲爱的 我想送你一份礼物才对
Honey, I want to give you a present.
我已经绞尽脑汁想了一天该送你什么
That's what I've been trying to do all day.
你是最不需要送我任何礼物的人了
You are the last person who should give me anything.
是你帮我走到今天
You got me here.
你抚养我到成功毕业 进入加州理工学院
You got me to graduation, to Caltech.
这都是你的功劳
You did it.
你的任务已经完成了
And you're done.
谢谢你 亲爱的 谢谢 我爱你
Thank you, sweetie. Thank you. I love you.
我想让你跟我一起去欧洲旅行
I want you to go to Europe with me.
什么
What?!
没错 我们会玩得很开心的
Yeah. We'll have a great time.
各种咖啡馆 博物馆
Cafés, museums,
再说了 欧洲对少女来说可不安全
plus, Europe is not safe for teenage girls.
你看过《飓风营救》吧
You've seen "Taken"?
你能想象爸爸要是收到那通电话会怎样吗
Could you imagine dad getting that phone call?
他能有什么特殊技能啊
What is his particular set of skills?
变魔术吗
Juggling?
老爸 我们能谈谈吗
Hey, Dad, can we talk?
-当然了 亲爱的 -私下里谈
- Sure, honey. - In private.
别那么用力 我无法呼吸了
Oh, not so hard. I can't breathe.
机器人的小笑话
Little robot humor.
我注意到你听到我的机器人笑话并没有笑
I noticed you didn't laugh at my robot joke.
出什么事了
What's going on?
大家都觉得贝丝超级好
Everyone thinks Beth is so great,
但我觉得她是个疯子
but I think she's crazy.
她已经针对我一整天了
She's been after me all day.
她为什么要针对你
Why would she be after you?
她觉得我爱上安迪了
She thinks I'm in love with Andy.
那你有吗
Are you?
没有 我的确关心他
No. I mean, I care about him.
他能逗我笑 我喜欢跟他一起玩
He makes me laugh. I like spending time with him.
当他不在你身边时 你会想他吗
Well, do you think about him when he's not around?
会吧
I guess.
有时候 我看到一些好笑的事 就会心想
Sometimes, I see something funny and I think,
"安迪一定超爱这个
"Oh, Andy would love that.
真希望他也在这里
I wish he were here
我就能跟他一起乐了"
so I could share it with him."
但是
But...
亲爱的 我知道我只是个机器人
Honey, I know I'm just a robot,
但在我看来那就是爱啊
but that sounds like love to me.
反正也无所谓了
Desn't matter anyway.
他爱着别人
He's in love with someone else.
或许我才是个疯子吧
Maybe I'm the crazy one.
我不是故意要打扰的
Don't mean to interrupt.
只是来道别一下
Just came to say goodbye.
贝丝和我打算开车出去兜兜风
Beth and I are going to take a drive,
欣赏夕阳的美景
try to catch the sunset.
好的 祝你们玩得开心
Okay, well, have fun.
好
Okay.
是海莉 海莉就是那个女孩
It's Haley. Haley's the girl.
你爱的是海...
You love Ha--
你们爱着对方
love each other!
走吧 我送你们出去
Come on. I'll walk you out.
你们要去哪儿啊
Where are you going?
你们爱着对方
You guys love each oth--
你们正在犯下一个巨大的错误
You're making a huge mistake!
准备好了吗
Ready?
快回来
Come back.
天啊 这下一定会很疼的
Oh, boy. This is gonna hurt.
快停下
Stop!
有人吗
Hello?
不要啊
No!
有人吗
Hello?
有谁能听到我说话吗
Can anybody hear me?
有人吗
Hello?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
你一定得帮帮我 我出了点事故
You've got to help me. I've been in an accident.
我需要你帮我找到我女儿
I-I need you to find my daughter.
好极了 谢谢
Oh, great. Thank you.
什么 你在干什么 你要去哪儿
What -- what are you doing? Where are you going?
你要带我去哪儿
Where are you taking me?
快把我放下
Put me down.
救命啊 我被人劫持啦
Help! I'm being taken!